glockapps.com 2019-12-06

# √ Privacy Policies ® G-Lock Apps

Thank you for visiting GLockApps official website located at [glockapps.com](https://glockapps.com/).

We at GlockApps (“GlockApps”, “Service”, “We”, “Our”, “Us”) know that our users (“You”, “Your”) care about how their personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”, “Data”) is used and shared, and We take Your privacy and security very seriously.

These Privacy Policies disclose our data collection methods, usage and confidentiality policies throughout our site. By visiting or using the GlockApps website, You acknowledge that You accept the practices and policies outlined in these Privacy Policies, and You hereby consent that We will collect, use, and share Your personal information in the following ways.

### 1\. Services We Provide at GlockApps

#### Email and IP Testing

We offer an email testing service (“GlockApps”) that allows us to collect data on Your behalf about the emails that You send. We provide You with the seed email list that enables Us to collect data about Your sender infrastructure and email placement. Such data includes the email address and IP address(es) the message is sent from, date and time of the event, message content, message headers and the details about how the mailbox providers treat the email (e.g., whether they put it in the Inbox or spam folder or block it).

 **Integration with MailChimp**

We integrated GlockApps with MailChimp to provide You with an easy way of testing Your MailChimp email campaigns.

GlockApps will never contact or modify Your existing subscribers or lists You have in MailChimp in any way.

We’ll create a new audience in Your MailChimp account in order to import Our test email addresses, and We’ll display a list of Your existing campaigns. When You choose to run a spam test for one of Your campaigns, We’ll email a copy of that campaign to Our test list.

If You receive the “Your current account plan with MailChimp doesn’t permit the creation of additional audiences (GlockApps seed list)” error message, You’ll have to delete an existing audience in Your MailChimp account to allow GlockApps to upload the seed list or upgrade to a higher plan with MailChimp.

By allowing GlockApps to connect to Your MailChimp account, You give GlockApps permission to perform the following actions:

  * retrieve the contents of Your MailChimp templates and campaigns for the purpose of performing email delivery tests;
  * create a new audience titled “GlockApps seed list”;
  * import GlockApps seed list into the “GlockApps seed list” in your MailChimp account. Note: Since MailChimp charges by subscribers, this may affect Your MailChimp pricing tier.
  * update the “GlockApps seed list” in Your MailChimp account in the event that GlockApps seed list changes.
  * create a new campaign and send it to the “GlockApps seed list” list for the purpose of performing an email delivery test.

GlockApps will ONLY contact subscribers in the “GlockApps seed list” list. Other lists and other subscribers in Your MailChimp account will NOT be contacted or modified in any way.

#### Bounce Email Tracking

We offer a bounce tracking tool that allows Us to collect data on Your behalf about bounce emails that You receive. We provide You with the proxy email address that enables Us to collect bounce emails on Your behalf and provide You with the bounce email analytics data. Such data includes the recipient’s email address, Bounce Type, ISP, Bounce Email Subject, Message-ID, From Email, From Domain, Report Date, Diagnostic Code, and Custom Fields if defined by You.

 **Integration with Amazon SES, Mailgun, SendGrid and SparkPost**

We integrated GlockApps with Amazon SES, Mailgun, SendGrid and SparkPost for bounce email tracking and analytics.

GlockApps will never contact or modify Your existing subscribers or lists you have in Amazon SES, Mailgun, SendGrid and SparkPost in any way.

We’ll set the GlockApps webhooks for bounce email tracking and We’ll collect only the bounce email data as stated above.

You acknowledge and agree that it is at Your discretion as to what data is collected in connection with the use of GlockApps, and therefore, You are solely responsible for the collection and use of any such data, ensuring that such collection and use are in accordance with Your privacy policies and all applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation any applicable data protection laws or regulations.

GlockApps operates under the domain https://glockapps.com. All data collected is the property of the customer (“You”) and is just hosted/facilitated by us. GlockApps stores this information securely on behalf of You. This information is only accessible by You.

### 2\. Collection of Information

#### 2.1. What Information Does GlockApps Collect Automatically?

You can visit our site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Our site does automatically collect information such as Your IP address, browser type, operating system, “cookie” information, and the page You requested for site trends and statistics, but this information does not personally identify You.

To protect the customer resources area from misuse, We actively monitor all logins into the system in addition to recording standard weblogs. We collect login dates and times as well as recording IP addresses on an individual basis. In addition, We record the details on all actions that are taken, also on an individual basis. This allows Us to perform individual analysis of patterns of activity for the purposes of detecting prohibited access and misuse of the resources in the system.

We do not receive or ever store any financial information such as credit card details and none of the information We collect is ever shared with any third parties outside of our immediate e-commerce provider.

The customer area presents a highly individualized facility for managing reports and raw data. In order to provide this facility, We have to record basic (non-financial) information about each user’s choice of purchase as well as recording their usage of the facility, for example, to customize the credits remaining for each user.

When We collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the website), We only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify You personally. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners, but We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify You personally.

#### 2.2. What Types of Cookies Does GlockApps Use?

“Cookies” are identifiers We transfer to Your computer or mobile device that allow Us to recognize Your browser or mobile device and tell Us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. You may change the preferences on our browser or mobile device to prevent or limit Your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent You from taking advantage of some of our website’s features. If You click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to You. These Privacy Policies do not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

glockapps.com uses anonymous session cookies. A session cookie only ever contains a unique identifier for managing session state and therefore does not contain any personally identifiable information. Session cookies are automatically deleted when the web browser is closed.

glockapps.com also uses third-party cookies, installed by [Google Analytics](https://google-analytics.com/) and [Facebook Pixel Code](https://connect.facebook.net/), to process statistical analyses of the user’s browsing habits, on the number of pages visited or the number of clicks the user makes on a page when browsing. We process the results of these analyses for statistical purposes on website user behavior, in order to improve and fine-tune website content. If You would like further information about third-party cookies used by glockapps.com, and information about how to manage or refuse them, click the links below:

#### 2.3. What Information Does GlockApps Ask You to Provide?

We ask You to provide your Personal Information such as Your first name, last name, email address, and username when You create an account with the Service. We ask You to provide Your SMTP settings such the SMTP server name, port number, SMTP login and password when You create a sending account with the service. We ask You to provide Your IMAP settings such the IMAP server name, port number, IMAP login and password when You connect to Your IMAP server to track bounce emails with the service. You can choose to not provide Us with certain information, but then You may not be able to register with Us or take advantage of some features of Our website.

We may ask You to provide personally identifiable information if You are signing up as Our reseller and partner. Some information about Your company, its size or other details may be required by Us via email while providing pre-sales support. When You contact the GlockApps support any details You provide are used only to help Us solve any issues You have and are destroyed once Your issue is dealt with. We do not make any of this information available to any third parties.

#### 2.4. What Information Do You Provide When Purchasing the Service?

When subscribing to our paid service, You will be asked for financial details such credit/debit card information, Your postal address, Your first name, last name and email address. The processing of the payments is carried out by the third party company 2checkout.com and on a separate secure server. We do not store any credit or debit card information on Our servers. 2checkout does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Immediately after You purchase the service our e-commerce partner will notify Us and will pass your contact information together with some limited purchase order information (e.g. purchase date, order reference number, service name, and price) to Us. We use this data to enable Your GlockApps paid account, to identify You in order to give You the full benefits of Your purchase including free technical support and to enable Us to set up a user account providing You with access to Our customer resources area. We do not make any of this information available to any third parties. For security purposes, the IP address of this transaction may be recorded.

### 3\. Security of Information

All information You provide to us is stored on Our secure servers. Any payment transactions are carried out by the third party over encrypted connections using SSL technology.

Your account is protected by a login and a password for Your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to Your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting Your login and password appropriately and limiting access to Your computer or device and browser by signing off after You have finished accessing Your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of Your account and other Personal Information We hold in our records, but We cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. Please remember that You control the information that You input and the data that is collected in connection with Your subscription to Our GlockApps services.

The service may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site, You must read that site’s privacy policy.

### 4\. Use of Information

The personal information You provide will be used for the purpose for which it was provided – to contact You, to process Your order, to activate Your account, to locate Your account in order to provide support. We may also use any information You have provided as reasonably necessary to provide notices regarding the products or services that You purchased.

Your personal data, including Your e-mail address, Your SMTP settings, and Your IMAP settings is used for internal purposes only and for testing email deliverability through Your SMTP server or email account and is never sold or shared with anyone outside of G-Lock Software or our authorized resellers, unless We disclose information in response to a law enforcement request.

Our administration staff may monitor site usage and use collected information to administer and maintain the privacy and security of the website.

Our support staff may use collected information to perform requested support tasks and any additionally supplied information will only be used for completion of the activity for which the data was provided.

We may share information with our billing company 2checkout. This is necessary for processing Your orders or troubleshooting. Your information may also be shared with G-Lock Software authorized resellers and partners who We may think would serve You better.

### 5\. Storage of Information

We store the information collected by GlockApps such as spam test reports, message headers, bounce email analytics, bounce reports, and DMARC reports in Your personal account on a secure AWS server in the US East (N. Virginia) region.

We will store the reports of spam tests for 12 months after the date of the test triggering. You can get the data via API and store it yourself if You need to access the reports after the 12-month period.

We will store the message headers for 30 days after the date of the test triggering. After the 30-day period, You will not have access to the headers in your reports.

The Sender Score history in the IP Reputation Monitor will be stored for 30 days.

Bounce email analytics will be stored for 90 days. Downloadable bounce email reports will be stored for 12 months.

DMARC reports will be stored for 3 months.

### 6\. Access to Information

You can access the information collected by GlockApps such as spam test reports, message headers, IP addresses tests, bounce email analytics, bounce reports, and DMARC reports in your account.

After your subscription cancelation or expiration, your paid account will be converted into the free account with limited features and data access. You will not have access to the tools such as IP Reputation Monitor, Bounce Monitor and DMARC Monitor and the data collected by these tools until you re-subscribe to a paid plan.

After your subscription cancelation or expiration or DMARC Monitor free trial expiration, you MUST delete the DMARC record pointing to glockapps.com in your domain’s DNS.

### 7\. Access and Correction of Your Personal Information

As an authenticated customer, You can enter the customer area. You can use the customer area to view Your contact and subscription details.

You can on request obtain a full report containing all of the personally identifiable information We have recorded about You.

You can contact Our customer support directly to request corrections to be made to any recorded information if You consider it to be incorrect.

If You have your account put on hold, You can contact Our customer support to attempt to have Your account reinstated.

### 8\. With Whom We May Share Your Personal Information

We may share Your information with Our billing company 2checkout.com if it is necessary for processing Your orders or troubleshooting.

We may share your information with G-Lock Software authorized resellers and partners who We may think would serve You better.

### 9\. Technical Support

When You contact the GlockApps support any details You provide are used only to help Us solve any issues You have and are destroyed once Your issue is dealt with.

We do not make any of this information available to any third parties.
